Welcome students, you all are welcome to my
YouTube channel. We will
meet again today with a new vacancy. The
vacancy that has come out today is from
ICICI Bank Recruitment 2013. The
total number of posts is
around 3560
[Music]
and the post name is Assistant Manager and the
vacancy has come out for other posts.
If we talk about the online date, then
your forms have started going online from 2nd February
and till when will they be filled, their last date is
18 years. The limit is that you should be 18 years old.
Qualification: Ten pass. Ten pass and graduate are
mandatory.
Selection process: Whatever the selection process,
you will be selected through interview. The
salary will be from 26000 to 64000 rupees.
You will get salary in this.
If we talk about job location, then you can apply for this from all over
India, from any state, from any
region, from any district.
How did you like the information given by me,
please tell me in the comment section. Video